buckrail.com 2019-04-03

# Privacy Policy - Buckrail - Jackson Hole, news

The Jackson Hole Buckrail Privacy Policy  
==============  
Last updated: May 1st, 2018

Buckrail LLC (“Buckrail” or “Jackson Hole Buckrail”) operates theBuckrailwebsite (http://www.buckrail.com).  
Jackson Hole Buckrail is a news aggregator for the geographical region of Jackson Hole, Wyoming and the surrounding area. Buckrail collects and aggregates user generated as well as Buckrail created content for distribution on the Internet.

Buckrail cares about your privacy. For this reason, we collect and use personal data only as it might be needed for us to deliver to you our products, services, websites, and mobile applications (collectively, our “Services”). This page informs you of Buckrail’s policies regarding how we collect, use, and disclose information from you and about you when you use the Buckrail Service.

This Privacy Policy applies to information Buckrail collects from all sources, including, but not limited to our websites, mobile sites, applications, widgets, conferences, events, and electronic newsletters or communications. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used herein have the same meaning as in our Terms and Conditions that are also accessible at https://buckrail.com.

. By

1\. Information Collection And Use

Buckrail collects Personal Information to provide, improve and deliver our Services. “Personal Information” for purposes of this Privacy Policy is the information that identifies you as an individual or relates to an identifiable person, including information that can be used to contact or identify you, such as your email address.

We collect Personal Information for the purpose of providing the Service,  
identifying and communicating with you, responding to your requests/inquiries,  
servicing your purchase orders, and improving our Service.

2\. Cookies and Log Data

A cookie is a small text file that is sent and stored on your computer or other connected device to identify your browser or to store information. Cookies may include an anonymous  
unique identifier. Cookies are widely used in order to make websites work, or work in a better, more efficient way. Buckrail uses cookies to collect information in order to  
deliver and improve our Service, and to display relevant content, products, services, and advertising. Buckrail may use the following cookies: session identifier cookies, functional cookies, flash cookies, advertising cookies, and social networking cookies.

You can stop cookies from being downloaded at any time by selecting the appropriate settings in your browser.. Most browsers provide a Help feature and tell you how to change your browser settings to accept , disable, or update cookies, or to notify you when receiving a new  
cookie. Please consult the “Help” section of your browser for more information or by visiting http://www.allaboutcookies.org.

If you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some features of the Buckrail Service and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

2.1 DoubleClick Cookie  
——————  
Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Service.  
Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve  
ads to our users based on their visit to our Service or other web sites on the  
Internet.

You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick Cookie for interest-based  
advertising by visiting the Google Ads Settings web page: https://tinyurl.com/ycymsnkp

2.2 Log Data  
Buckrail may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit Buckrail.com or use our Service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.  
In addition, we may use third-party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase the functionality of and improve the Service. These third-party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.  
3\. Behavioral Remarketing

Buckrail uses remarketing services to advertise on third party web sites  
to you after you visited our Service. Buckrail and our third party vendors, use  
cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our  
Service.

3.1 Google

Google (a subsidiary of Alphabet Inc.) provides Google AdWords remarketing service. p  
You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize  
the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings web page (noted above).

Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser  
Add-on for your web  
browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with  
the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google  
Analytics.  
For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the  
Google Privacy & Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy.

3.2 Facebook

Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc.You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by  
visiting this page: https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950?helpref=related

To opt-out from Facebook’s interest-based ads follow these instructions  
from Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/?entry_product=ad_settings_screen

Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral  
Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also  
opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the  
Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA, the Digital Advertising Alliance of  
Canada, or the European Interactive  
Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe,  
or opt-out using your mobile device settings.  
For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit  
Facebook’s Data Policy: https://www.facebook.com/policy.php

4\. Service Providers

Buckrail may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate or provide our Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services  
and/or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.  
These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform  
specific tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use your  
information for any other purpose.

5\. Communications

Buckrail may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters,  
marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of  
interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these  
communications from Buckrail by following the unsubscribe link or instructions  
provided in any email we send or by contacting us (at the contact information listed below).

6\. Security

Buckrail follows generally accepted standards to store and protect the Personal Information we collect both during transmission, once received, and stored, including utilization of encryption where appropriate. Buckrail retains Personal Information only for as long as necessary to provide the Services and thereafter for a variety of legitimate legal or business purposes. These retention purposes may include: (1) as mandated by law, contract or similar obligations applicable to our business operations; (2) for preserving, resolving, defending, or enforcing our legal/contractual rights; or (3) needed to maintain adequate and accurate business and financial records.  
However, please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or  
method of electronic storage is 100% secure and we are unable to guarantee the  
absolute security of the Personal Information we have collected from you.

7\. International Transfer

Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to—and  
maintained on—computers located outside of your state, province, country or  
other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than  
those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to  
us, please note that we transfer the information, including Personal  
Information, to United States and process it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such  
information represents your agreement to that transfer.

8\. Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)  
If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), Buckrail’s legal basis for collecting and using Personal Information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Information we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.  
Buckrail may process your Personal Information because:  
• Buckrail needs to perform a contract with you  
• You have given us permission to do so  
• For payment processing purposes  
• To comply with the law  
9\. Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. Buckrail aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Information.  
If you wish to be informed what Personal Information we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.  
In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:  
• The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you. Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Information by contacting us.  
• The right of rectification. You have the right to have your Persona Information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.  
• The right to object. You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Information  
• The right of restriction. You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your Personal Information.  
• The right to data portability. You have the right to be provided with a copy of the Personal Information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.  
• The right to withdraw consent. You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where Buckrail relied on your consent to process your Personal Information.  
Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.  
You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).

10\. Links To Other Websites

The Buckrail Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by Buckrail. If  
you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s  
site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you  
visit. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy  
policies or practices of any third party websites or services.

11\. Compliance with California Online Privacy Protection Act  
California Online Privacy Protection Act (“CalOPPA”) is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a Privacy Policy. The law’s reach stretches beyond the borders of California to require a person or company in the United States that operates websites collecting Personal Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous Privacy Policy on its website. See http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf  
According to CalOPPA we agree that users can visit our site anonymously.

12\. Children’s Privacy  
——————  
Only persons age 18 or older have permission to access the Buckrail Service. The Buckrail  
Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 (“Child” or “Children”).  
We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from Children. If you are a parent or guardian and you learn that your Children  
have provided Buckrail with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become  
aware that we have collected Personal Information from a Child without verified parental consent, we will take steps to remove that Personal Information  
from Buckrail’s servers.

13\. Changes To This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of June___, 2018 and will remain in  
effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future,  
which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.  
Buckrail reserves the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and  
you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the  
Service after Buckrail posts any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page  
will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to  
abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

If Buckrail makes any material changes to this Privacy Policy, Buckrail will notify you  
either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a  
prominent notice on our website.

14\. Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:(307) 222-8609 or info@buckrail.com.
